Um Jasher everyone um I believe I'm live
now so you should be able to uh see me.
Thank you very much for um joining me on
this uh beautiful day for this very
beautiful um moment. So um we'll start
with a little invocation to divine
mother because um I guess any other way
would not be appropriate.
[Music]
Oh
sh matsa.
I
Shag
[Music]
moin sindu. Mornings.
is for us.
[Music]
Smith.
All glories to divine mother. First of
all, I offer my bisense to the divine in
you with whose grace we're all here
right now this
moment. Um, welcome to the launch of uh
Tantra Sadna. It's a very big moment for
for me, for you, for for our team
because we've been working on it uh for
almost three years but out of which two
years um absolutely with a full-on team
and I pretty much started working on
this ever since we launched uh the sad
app which was almost uh 3 years ago.
Now there are many many misconceptions
about tantra um in the world out there.
I I thought um I wasn't sure how much
detail I should cover today with you
when it comes to tantra. But I think it
might help to understand the origin of
tantra a little bit. So you know the
difference like you can differentiate
from let's the sh karma in tantra which
is maran chhatan vashikaran samohan
vidan tambhan and so on and the real
tantra or the so-called bhamacha
practices because of which tantra has u
gained uh a notorious kind of reputation
in many parts of the world. You see
tantr
practices actually existed even before
the vic era and the tribes of Rdra Lord
Shiva were the first ones to propagate
tantra. In fact all of scriptures that
he has spoken are called agama. Agama is
where ma goddess mother goddess asks a
question and Shiva answers and nigum is
where the reverse happens where mother
is answering the question and Lord Shiva
is ask asking those questions. So they
existed before even the Vic practices
were there. And if you want to
understand the various species um or the
races uh that were there of dwas,
manovas and and rdras and yakshas and
and others um I encourage you to just
touch upon a little um my book uh legend
of the goddess there I've covered it.
So as the Vedas evolved and in the
beginning we only had three Vedas. uh
there was uh Rick, there was Sam, there
was Azure and there was no Aturva
because
Aturva documented or at that time the
transmission was oral. Um all the
practices of tantra as we know today.
However, what we know today has been
polluted uh to a great degree. But those
all those practices emerged from a turva
and it was praser rishi who asked vyasa
to get a turva included as one of the
main vedas and due to his influence in
the world uh political as well as his
connections with hustinapur at that time
uh he was somebody who could get that
done prior to that if you read sanka
yoga we had three of everything uh three
ga uh three modes of material nature
three kinds of jagna three kinds of
suka, three kinds of duka, uh three
kinds of karma and three kinds of
everything and
trua and which was actually also the
basis of Kashmir shaism's trick
philosophy which is a different branch u
altogether but tantric practices that
emerged at the
time had five different schools of
tantra there was the dakshachar there
was vamachar there was kolaachar and
there was uh Samya and then there was
Mishrachar. Now Mishrachar was called
the mixed path. So which had left-handed
practices and right-handed practices. It
emerged much later and then it was
particularly taken up in parts of India
notably Bihar, Uttar Pradesh and West
Bengal. Now if you look at for example
the music today, what happens? We are no
longer singing pure ragas in our
mainstream music. Our mainstream music
has fusion. It's got western influence.
We are talking about chords. We're
talking about harmonization. We're
talking about modes and scales and
whatnot. Similarly, what happened when
the original tantric practices were
prevalent in India which as I shared
with you had been existing from the
pre-vedic era. when those practices
became very dominant about 150 years ago
two significant events happened. One was
um this person called Sir John Woodruff
who was a a magistrate a judge in India
British guy and he penned down um by the
name of Arthur Revlon a book called the
serpent power and also Shaki and Shaktal
I think so with those two books he took
Tantra to the west but what he did was
something quite remarkable he spoke
about the pristine nature of Tantra as
opposed to the tantric practices as as
such. Until then, tantra was seen as um
hiddonistic kind of u set of practices,
obscure occult practices that nobody
knew what they were about. And it didn't
help the world that we had a lot of fake
tantrics who would just smear ash and so
on and pretend to be tantric whereas
they didn't really understand the
essence of tantra most of them. So the
west understood and if you look at for
example kria yoga or kundalini yoga
kundalini is a pure tantric concept. Now
kundalini forms part of what we call
samyachchar which is an entire internal
worship of mother goddess almost
formless to the to the great to a great
degree. Now when that was happening
alongside around 1905 there was another
American oultist called I think Pier
Bernard or something. He was mostly
interested in the sexual aspect of
tantra. Now really there was no sexual
aspect as such but there was the concept
of punch makar. Uh punchmakar is matasa
which is fish madira which is wine. Uh
mas which is meat. mudra which is
handlocks or parched grains um or or
bodily positions poses um in in tantra
and fifth was mun which was actual
culation. It so happened that the
Americans took a shine to this and
eventually what happened they took out
all the rituals. So no chanting, no
invocation, no divinity and it became
only about just sexual experiences and
sensual experiences. Now that's one
thing that was happening. Parallelly
what happened in India prior to that
period around 1500 years ago or even
before our scriptures went overseas and
Buddhist monks were the first ones to
take them overseas notably to Tibet. In
Tibet it got mixed with what we call
what they used to call the B religion.
One of the original shamanic religions
of Tibet. So there they got mixed. They
used to worship a goddess called Tara.
And from there emerged a practice called
Mahajin Karma which original name of it
was
Mahajinatara. Mahajintara. Mahajinatara
Karma. And it became Mahajin Karma which
involved a female and a male. And this
became very popular. So when those
shamanic practices came back to India,
all the states that share a border with
Tibet uh notably Sikkim or Kashmir or
Himachal Pradesh um and I think one more
state that shares Arunachal Pradesh I
think. So there tantra took on a
different form and alongside we had this
sh karma in tantra and eternally if you
look at our basic nature we are always
looking for a shortcut we are always
wanting to do whatever it is that we
want to get accomplished in an easier
fashion faster better cheaper and so on
so when when a vamachari uh somebody
practicing the left-handed path of
tantra or a mish Rajari would be sitting
in the cremation ground praying. It
would attract a lot of attention. Now I
know some of you are not going to
believe me and I'm not here to convince
you. I'm not here to convince you about
the origins of Tantra or my own research
or my experiences or the knowledge or
wisdom I've received from my own guru
and other tantric masters. But my job is
to put the truth out there for you and
the rest it's up to you to believe or
not believe to take it or leave it and
that's entirely your call. It's not my
prerogative. It's yours.
So when that was happening um people
started believing um that these tantric
the so-called tantrics could actually
change their fortune and combined with
the tribal practices and the shamanic
practices the real tantra whose core
objective was a realization of shaki
realization of mother goddess started to
disappear and dissipate. It became all
about just obscure practices that people
thought made sense or didn't make sense
but maybe some tantric is doing some
kritya it's called some priyoggas
launching maybe maharan karma or shanti
karma even sometimes but all the other
shat karma that I spoke about the six
kind of u actions you can perform with
tantra now across this these path that
we spoke about uh one of the path is
vamachar which is a left-handed path of
tantra which has um like I spoke about
these practices mahachin, latasan,
shavasadan, panchmundi, navmundi and so
on and uh many many bahov kinds of bahu
puja although tantra is not just about
bhav puja or dyupa. There is s tantra
which is linked to the sun worship.
There is gpatya tantra which is linked
to worship of lord ganesha. There is
shakt which is mother goddess which this
app is predominantly concerned with and
then there is shav tantra which is
praying to um lord shiva and then there
is vashnav tantra which is praying to a
form of lord vishnu and pancharatra
texts of uh vashnavism are talk about
those tantric practices and one of the
core texts if you want to read is
Lakshmi tantra I've spoken a great deal
about did uh in the past as well in
Kashmir a certain school of thought
started to emerge called kalachar which
is one of the core one of the original
uh tantric schools. Now ka emerged from
the word kula. Koula means a clan or a
lineage. So in this practice it was in
this school it was strictly guru to
disciple oral transmission and these
were also the days when there were no
manuscripts uh no written word. This was
all before uh all of that emerged. Now
Kachar talked about the highest good
realizing of the great potential but as
I shared with you when the influence of
Tibet and other practices emerged um and
and they mingled kachar took on a
different form and if you want to read
if you want to know more you can read
kular nav tantra where you would
understand a bit more of the kala
practice. Now when all of this
happened there is one called duh dvaar
which is a form of dakshina. Divvyachar
is the divine conduct. Divvyar was first
given to bhagan persuarama by lord
dutatria. So he expounded on tripur
raisia and provided that esoteric
knowledge and wisdom to lord persuarama.
The beauty of Dvachar is you can realize
the 10 forms of mahavidyas the mahavidya
which this app is about that medium that
we have created for you through dvyar.
So what I have done in this and all the
practices that you see in this app
across the 10va vidyas I have personally
done every single one of them. There is
one of China Dvi which is called
kandamandanda sadena or sometimes nakand
sadha. There in the app you see actual
offering of the physical body but in the
in the actual sadha you offer it
mentally. So that's the only difference.
All the other sadas that you see from
kali to kamlat mika I've done every
single one of them. So this app that
I've created it is based on my distilled
experience. And the reason for creating
this app is to share with you the world
of tantra in a way that you're not
misguided and you're not fearful, you're
not afraid so that you can still at
least understand the rituals involved.
So you can still at least understand
um what it takes to invoke goddess. And
there is something which is very
important to mention here when we talk
about tantra. Please understand that the
10 mahavidyas can only be
invoked as mother goddess. So kali is
not just kali. Kali is
mali. If if somebody is referring to
goddess as like kali tara this and that
and the other as if they're like friends
or just this that is not the way to go.
Although the ideal the highest goal of
tantra is to become one with your object
of worship. So you become one with your
deity. If you become one with your
object of worship, then you embody the
same qualities as your object of
worship. That is really the that is
where it differs from a pure bacti yoga
or dueta which says I am jatma. You are
paramatma. I can never be you. I'm not
trying to be you but I'm just happy you
are there. But in tantra we say let me
purify myself to such a degree. Break
all my conditioning in a fashion that oh
mother goddess you reside in me. Now
yogis, yakshinis and pishachinis and
other lower forms of energies you can
invoke either as as a sister like assume
them to be a sister or a friend or or
something you know sagari bhar and so
on. But mother goddess you can only ever
invoke as a child. So she only is ever
invoked as a mother. Which means there
is always an element of dyachar in
proper tantric worship no matter
how rigorous or crude the rituals might
appear to be. So in this app tantra app
um tantra satan app what we have done is
is I've exposed you to the purest form
of worship. There is no short karma in
this app. uh which means you cannot do
maranu chardan and so on but there is a
way for you to gain the grace of divine
mother and do you require initiation of
course not it follows the path of self
initiation and because I've personally
experienced these um sadhas and what I
have shared with you is a path to get to
the main ritual so by the time you get
to the main ritual you would already
have developed a certain devotion
towards divine mother or that particular
form from like I said Kali to Kamlat
Mika and everyone in between whether
that's matara or matriund maharvi or
dumawati and so on so just so you know
um there is not a tantric text any major
tantric text that I haven't read so I
know exactly what I'm talking about um
in the last I am this body is 45 years
old so in the last more than I would say
35 years at
least I have done extensive study of
tantra so there is not a major tantric
scripture or text or the vic source of
it that I haven't read I've read all of
them and the sadas that I share with you
it's not like I read in a book and I
thought oh I should go and and try this
sadena with you I was initiated into all
those sadness which authorizes me to
share it with those who can benefit from
it and I have kept the whole thing very
satwic very beautiful but very
authentic. So my own first guru uh not
my first guru but my main guru uh Nagaba
my pretty much only dika guru in life um
he was a tantra Samrat he actually was
uh given
that and he spent 12 years in kamaka he
spent eight years on the cremation
grounds of Banaras Manikarnad and he
spent two years on a boat he spent uh 8
years in vindachal or or 12 years I I
forget now and he spent 9 years standing
and every year he would do jal dhara jal
vihar and panchagni dhuna so he spent
his entire life doing various tantric
practices and from him I got a couple of
satas and then there was swami
karunaandanda he was one of the finest
tantrics I've ever met throughout his
life he never missed navasa when he woo
his collic and kapalik sadha I was
initiated ated into those sadas by him.
He also gave me Mahachin Brahma and
Latas sadhan and shavasadhan and
punchmundi and navmundi I got from naga
baba and then there was the first one
that uh my own uncle who initiated me
into ara sadhana and he initiated pipla
sadhana. You will see what those sadnas
are when you um experience uh the app.
Now to to you and for
you I've made it
extremely simple because I really
believe we must democratize sadha and
you might be wondering if you're not
initiated into it can any harm befall
can any harm come on you the answer is
absolutely not when you are going to do
the preliminary practices that we've
configured in each world And I will
share with you what those are in a
moment. You are pretty much
self-initiating yourself. And I have
this firm belief that if you are opening
this app to pray to goddess with the
highest good, how can any harm come your
way? as they
say that our intentions may may not be
all that noble as children, but a mother
is never kumata. A mother is is always
only going to ever want the absolute
best for you. And there is no other way
that a mother would
operate. So I think um we can perhaps
pretty much get into the app now. I'd be
happy to give you a little
demo maybe um just bear in mind two
things.
One, it may seem a little cumbersome to
you using this
app, but bear in
mind there is a method to this madness.
There is a reason I've created this app
the way it is done.
And I can share with you that reason.
It's not like I have to keep it a
mystery. The primary reason is if you're
not prepared to to do self
exploration. If you're not prepared to
work for your sadena, then you are also
not ready to be initiated into it. Then
you're also not ready to actually do it.
So even though it may seem like a game
but please even for a moment don't think
it's a game. The reason it may look like
a game is because I wanted you to
experience the immersive nature of each
world where you'll be performing that
sadena. And thanks to technology and
thanks to our amazing uh amazing
development partners um all overseas um
Alexander and his team who did a
phenomenal job over the last two years
in building and even going beyond our
expectations with what we wanted done.
Uh even on a like a smaller kind of
phone, lower quality phone or basic
phone uh it works without heating up the
phone. it it works phenomenally well and
so on. The app size is a little little
large but please don't complain about
that. We are doing our best uh to do
what we can. It will reduce uh in the fe
in the future but right now
um I think to download 2GB or 1.3 GB of
data worship of mother goddess is the is
the smallest easiest thing anybody can u
be expected to do. Now going back to to
this if you are performing this it may
seem that oh I have to find my way
around it but the reason I've made it
that way the reason we've configured it
that way is because I'd like you to work
a little I'd like you to enjoy the
journey a little it would benefit you
from experiencing that world and doing
the things you u ought to be doing in
that so that when you go and perform the
main ritual of each world you are
truly in it you are truly devoted so
there is no way to hasten the process
that we have created uh in here so
you're always going to start your
journey from
u mahali that's the first mahavidya
now we could have opened uh it in a
fashion that you could go to any world
first. But you know there is a beautiful
verse in Laalita
Sasunama Mahantra Mahamantra Mahayantra
Mahasana
Mahayagarhya Mahabhu Puja. Oh mother
goddess you are Mahhatantra the greatest
tantra. You are Mahamantra the greatest
mantra the sonic energy and tantra is
the physical energy the expansion of
consciousness. The word tantra itself
means means that tan means so there is a
word called tan matra you might be
knowing that it means
um our
our psychical experiences
uh our sensual experiences but sensory
but psychical experiences shabaspuras
rub gun touch sight taste smell and so
on five of those and then t is also from
the word thread
And th is it means two things expansion
as well as protection thras or
expansion. So one that expands your
consciousness is
tantra. You cannot hope to expand your
consciousness if you are not going to
break the tendencies of the mind. One of
which could be laziness. That oh just
give it to me on a platter and I'll take
it and and I'll run with it. I want you
to work for it. What I have done is I
have really simplified it for you, but
ultimately it's um it's something that
I'd like you to work for
because the objective of creating this
app is only and only to enrich your
life. And if you for a moment think of
me as a doctor and think of let's say
yourself as a patient. I know you're
very impatient, but let's say you're a
patient. um you're a patient then I must
give you the advice that I believe will
benefit you as opposed to the advice
that I believe will benefit me and
that's really the basis of this app um
of this so you will be praying to divine
mother uh in her purest form as I was
explaining mahantra maha mantra mahay
yantra mahasna you have the greatest
seat and the greatest seat is one's
heart the purest heart and mahay yagakra
the greatest yoga but you are prayed in
a karma in a
sequence. So maha
yagaradha mahabhav puja that oh divine
mother even the great bhavva lord shiva
praise to you uh you are if at least not
praise to you you're reverred even by
him. So it is with that sentiment that
you're going to benefit the most if you
use this app and it is with that
sentiment that I've created um this app.
So u I think I have
um spoken enough uh why don't I take you
um into the app shall we? So I'm going
to share my screen with you.
Um screen sharing is
um so please give me a
moment.
[Music]
Okay. So I hope
uh you
can see this and
here and
uh everything
uh
now I just have to quickly ensure
[Music]
that
sorry okay great now just anybody in the
comment um in in on YouTube comments
I've I've opened it on the side so just
now can you please just somebody say you
can see my screen
Yes. Can you see the Yeah. Okay. Great.
Lovely. Lovely. Now, uh, so my voice is
clear. The music is not too loud,
right? Okay.
Great.
Um, okay. Lovely. All right. So, this is
what we called the map, the realm map of
uh 10
Mahavidyas. And um so when we so once
you log into the app there's a tutorial
that you will go through and once you go
over the tutorial it will uh teach you
all aspects of the app that you uh need
to know. Now once you're in it you will
see this world uh and it starts with
let's say
Khali. So if I go to Hali um you can see
the main sad that is there for each
world
and so I'm just going to give you a
little preview although uh the app will
be downloadable I believe on itself.
So app is called tantra sadhana
app and this is uh to awaken the 10
mahavidyas. So there is makali, matara,
matriundi,
mahabueshwari and out of love um you can
just call them okay bhneshwari but it's
always ma and uh and then there is
mabharvi each mother goddess each form
of hers um has a world of her own that
you will have to experience and find
things in that and I will explain what I
mean in a moment and then maduma would
be mabili
and uh Mama
Dangi and
Makam the last
one. So if I go back here for a moment,
you have a companion in
this beautiful little dog and um so this
dog is not just an NPC what we call
non-playable character. instead it's in
fact it's a um
very sorry somebody said please
background music is so loud okay I
couldn't hear that is it better now
um yes
um
okay so okay sorry um that I hope messed
up your experience a little I hope did
not Anyway, you haven't missed out on
much. So, we have this uh
character uh like a dog and there are
different dogs to choose from because
every good tantric ought to have a good
dog and uh this dog actually whatever
you choose and name you give that dog.
So, I'm just going to leave it um there.
So, there are um like as I said uh 10 or
or a few different varieties to choose
from. They actually the dog you choose
will actually guide you in the world. Uh
you'll be able to navigate the world uh
with the dog. So if you don't know where
to go, uh you will be able
to see um the dog and um you'll be able
to see the path through the dog. Sorry,
I'll go back here. Now what I'll do um I
will actually take you into this world.
So, I'm going to begin the
quest. I hope it's already loaded. If
not, okay, you're
lucky. So, when the first time you you
log in, each world will kind of give you
a little tutorial. So, um so this
tutorial is
um yes. Um somebody's asking, can you
stream it from your phone to TV? Of
course you can. Uh you can do anything
you want. Remember you're a great
tantric now. So you should be able to
accomplish
anything. So
um so this initial world gives you the
preview and you are guided by Viasa. At
every step um in the app you are guided
by Vasa. So he will tell you what your
next step is, what you ought to do and
if you ever lose your way, you can call
upon the dog uh whatever dog, whatever
name you give your dog. Now I do want to
mention one thing here. Please know that
the app is completely free. Um but
there's a caveat uh but caveat doesn't
mean you have to pay. So you can use
this entire app, do all the rituals, uh
do all the practices, explore all the
worlds completely free. You don't have
to pay even a scent if you um don't wish
to. Uh so I've just stopped the music
for a moment. So you don't have to pay
anything at all. It's completely free
because we did not want any barriers for
anybody to be able to explore uh the
beauty of sanatan dharma or aturvda and
our practices that have been existing
since eons. So you should be able to
experience the glory of it. So as I said
uh you so in in the beginning of each
world you see vasa. So you go and what
I'm doing here is I'm controlling this
like uh with my uh left and right thumb.
So if I touch on right side, you see
this uh eye thing come up. If I move my
thumb a little, then it shows you a
different view. And if I do the left
one, then I can move. So I'm just going
to go
to
Vasa and
uh sorry
um
so I started going the other
way. Talk about
mindfulness. Now you can pay obience to
him. So we have we have um taken care of
our culture and heritage. Actually it's
a little thing. I'm just going to show
you how he pays the obesian. So you can
choose from a male avatar or a female
avatar. Um so you can just
u um do that. So a lot of people are
saying they cannot find the app on play
store. I believe it will be launched um
sometime tonight. Um and the team can
tell you in this um you can also go to
the website
tantr.app. So and then you can hear
vas namaste. So you stand at the
threshold of a path few dare to
walk. The shavas sadhana dissolves fear
burns afflictions and in you can also
obviously stop the voice over and you
can just go yes master because uh you
guys belong to the great yoga kali yoga
you all don't have any time so that's uh
fabulous. So I'm told that app is
already there um live on the app stores.
So I don't know why you can't find
it. So Vasa is always chanting one of
D's this thing. But you can move away
from him if you so wish. He's told you
what to do. If you tap on this eye
icon, you can see what all you need to
do in this
world. So find the owl to solve a
puzzle. Find a chanting ground and chant
and find the donkey to solve a puzzle
ingredient bundles collected blah blah
blah. And I'll tell you
basically there are two I will stop the
the music for a moment. Um there
are there are
two preparatory rituals that you have to
do in this app before you can unlock the
main ritual. There are two preparations
you have to do and that is
chanting as well as fire offerings. So
japa and jagna you have to do for at
least 11 days before you can start to do
the main ritual. So main ritual is
either for 21 days or 40 days depending
on which sadena it is. Now 11 days of
preparation rituals or prerequisites and
21 days minimum of main ritual or 40
days depending on which sadena for
example in matripur sunduri sadha the
shriantra sadna it's minimum 40 days so
you have to do those rituals and that so
that let's say we talk about makali so
that's 21 days plus 11 days 33 days so
once you do 33 days you have completed
one cycle after you completed that one
cycle, the other the next world will
unlock for you. And if you really like
this ritual, you can then come back any
time and just do the ritual or or do the
whole world once again if you so wish.
It's entirely your choice. But you need
to go through one full cycle which is
minimum of 33 days before the new world
will unlock for you. And somebody's
asking can householders uh do this puja?
Uh yes, male, female, children,
householders,
uh householders who are not good at
holding down their houses. Even those uh
whether you are uh menstruating or not,
whether you have eaten or not, whether
you eat non-vegetarian, vegetarian,
pescatarian, egotarian, whatever you are
uh you can do these sadas. It's all part
of dvy, the highest form of worship
because pretty much you are fully
immersed in it. you are performing
manasic worship uh the mental chanting.
So u somebody is saying app is not
downloading at all. It is showing the
app is not compatible with your device.
I don't know uh about that. So you'll
have to figure it out. Maybe please feel
free to write to the support team. Now
by the way this is available in both
Hindi and English. So um if I go here
and I go to settings and I go to
language I can see everything in Hindi
now. Uh but I will just go back to
English. So now as you know Vasa asked
me to go and find the owl. So I'm just
going to uh turn the music back on. I
hope it's uh
not too too loud. And I'm going to go
uh and go to the owl. Now, in case I
don't know where this owl is, I can call
upon
Aikida. Um but I will demonstrate that
in a
moment. So, by the way, we also have
these uh relics
throughout. Um so, if you collect those,
unlock those symbols, what you do is you
gain points. and I'll tell you.
So, sorry, there is a message.
Um,
okay.
Um, so you
can so then it tells you the
significance of that symbol. It's
related to that
goddess. So, you earn points.
Now I wanted to tell you about the the
the how it works. Basically for every
ritual that you do you earn points and
points give you the mudras. So if you
ever want to buy the ingredients from
the shop internally you can do that or
you can simply do the rituals and you
will learn enough mudras to buy it. You
never have to to uh pay a dime like I
said to buy any of this.
Now if I go back
here. So this is the owl. Namaste. Ma
Kali's mantra is so we will be improving
some of this voice over. So you'll have
to solve this puzzle um to see to gain
some points. If you don't want to solve
this puzzle, you can simply go to the
shop and straight away buy the
ingredients for the yagna that you need.
to see what this looks like. So, I'm
just going to actually first the uh the
tutorial was
there. If I press on this um this thing
here, the question mark sign, then I can
see what I need to complete. But if if
you are somebody who doesn't have the
patience um because you're very special
and you always want everything now, then
you can always click on this. It's going
to use a clue. Uh, so if I use one clue,
then I am now only three steps away from
solving
this. There you go. You have unlocked
Mali's mantra.
So, so I've just stopped the this thing.
Now,
now I need to find the chanting ground
for example. I won't show you the whole
ritual uh but
uh but you you uh need to find
enchanting ground. So what I can do I
can either go look for it myself which
is perfectly okay. You have the the
right to do that to explore the world
and if you do that you will find more
relics and things on the way or I can
feed Aikida. In this case the dog's name
is Akida. That's the default name.
So, I tapped on that icon that you saw
for feeding and there you
go. It was a good sport. All
right. So,
um and is very happy with you. He's
happy to now lead you to your
path. So, now you don't have to and you
earn 10 points for feeding him. So, if I
press it here on that, so he's going to
lead me to the chanting ground.
Where are you kid?
Okay, there he is. So, I just have to
now
um follow
him, which means I don't have to use my
own brain.
[Music]
Um, which I'm sure you can like reserve
for better things.
Um, but see, I I saw this thing. So,
what you see in the in my hand is a
staff. So, this is like a tantric
magical staff and what you have these
little things are ingredients. So
whenever you see them, collect that
bundle because as I said, I would like
you to explore and work towards it. So
you'll have to collect these bundles to
be able to do the jugna because each
jugna uses ingredients uh sacred
ingredients. And if you don't want to
spend time, you can always buy that in
the
shop. But like I said, you don't have to
pay even a scent. All of that is
completely free if you are willing to do
the
ritual. So I just saw this one more
thing. So I'm going to collect that as
well. And if I see this lit up thing.
This is my chanting
ground. So Aikita is blocking my
chanting ground. Aikita, what are you
doing?
Okay. So, so I think uh
Yeah. So, right now um
there's you have arrived at the chanting
ground like a typical the ruins of an
angel. He was just in his own world.
Now I'm getting given Vasa gives me some
instructions to
um so then um this you can choose
whether you wish to chant 27, 54 or 108
times. It if you tap on it, it'll tell
you how long it will take you. 54 times
and so on. And uh there is auto
chanting. Listen carefully to every
syllable of her mantra. Okay. So, I'm
just going to say yes. So, it's going to
sit
down. You can chant internally and you
can turn this on
or I can turn off the sound and just
chant internally or and I can tap
anywhere to progress to the next bead if
I don't want to. I can tap anywhere on
the screen or like I said, I can do the
auto mode. So I won't go through this
whole thing. So if I go
back, stop
chanting. Now I may also show you the
shop this thing.
So what we have is uh the shop shows you
the mudras you can buy. There is for the
fire offerings for the clues or for the
dog if you want the dog to guide you.
But like I said if you do the chanting
or if you do yagna or if you do other
rituals uh you don't have to buy
anything. um as you um can as you go
along you will keep gathering points and
if you get points you're getting mudra.
So even if you want to buy something you
can but you can always pick anything.
For example for jugna you can just go
around collect all those bundles and do
your jugna completely free. You can
solve the puzzle completely free and
everything else in the app including the
main ritual. So I'm saying this again
and again because over and over again we
repeatedly face this flack a lot.
Anytime there is any price for anything
we get a whole lot of people telling us
dharma should be free, this should be
free, that should be free and uh
sometimes uh it
really wastes my team's time to go
through all those queries relentlessly
and to put up with all the trolling. So
this is completely free. Um, but all you
have to do is do the the map, uh, do
the, um, the rituals. If I go back, by
the way, that's your, uh, profile. If I
go back to the now, the realm for a
moment. Now, here you see which day you
are on of your sacred preparation. So,
as I shared with you, first 11 days uh,
is the preparation rituals before you
unlock ma shavadana. in this case. And
you would have to do over 11 days at
least 1,08 chance and 11 fire offerings.
11 times Jagna and 1,08 chance. So once
you've done that, you'll be good. Now I
would love to show you the third ritual,
but for that you'll have to wait 11
days and at least I should have done at
least 1,08 chance. That's when that
ritual will be unlocked.
But there is uh another way I could show
you the main ritual. So if in your
message uh if you say uh do you want to
see the main
ritual? Anybody wish to see the main
ritual? Okay, good.
Okay. Yeah, you can eat onion, garlic.
can um uh eat anything.
Um even for all the sadnas I give you,
you know, I I never stop people from
eating um whatever they want to eat.
It's entirely your decision. I've spoken
a fair bit about it. Anyway, so I'm
going to stop sharing. Uh the reason I'm
going to stop sharing is because uh you
are very lovely people and if you want
to see the main ritual, then I'll have
to share um a different screen. So, we
took a screen screen grab of the main
ritual.
Um, now I'm just going to So, what
happens when you hit uh get to the main
ritual? Um, you
[Music]
will so go here.
So obviously the whole ritual is pretty
long. Uh it's not 30 minutes because
there is something else in this video.
Uh but I will show you the glimpses. So
this is
shad and
uh
right. So
once any specific nyas or
prerequisites like I
said it's it's the highest form of
worship. The cleaner your heart is the
more you will benefit. Uh it may seem
like it's a game but like I said it's
not a game. This is just a medium for
you to experience
um this um so people are asking is it
safe to do these sadnas at home? Yes, of
course it's um if it wasn't I wouldn't
have put them in there. See you must
never ever have any fear of anything.
It's very important to be fearless in
life. Can a mother ever harm you? and uh
you know and and really just experience
it for yourself and see when I launched
Sadnapp you know so many people were
wondering oh do these things um actually
even ever work will this be of any use
uh but shouldn't it be done and then
over the last 3 years we saw so many
lives being transformed and people
writing to us almost every single day
with great things and they benefited
from
She is to be woripped internally. This
is this is of highest kind. So I'll let
you see bit
of the
hope you can hear the
verse. I've painstakingly recorded every
single verse uh myself.
So I'm just going to go a little
further. So this is part of kapalik
sadhana. It is always done before ashav
sadhana. So I have documented that
entire process um including the mantras
everything. And you do this chanting.
I'm just screaming through and then you
get to the you mount the
courts the sh the
shva and then you start making those
offerings. Now the shad main ritual
starts. As you can see it's 8 minutes
long. So I'm just going to take you
further.
So I'm just going to take you further to
show you what happens when this ritual
is complete.
Brave seeker, I am Kali. I am the
essence of all beings living and dead.
I am pleased with your relentless
persistence. So today I will show you.
Yes, I am Kie.
Gotcha.
You have called upon me with devotion
and I have heard you. Your penance and
courage have brought you into my
embrace, my child. As a reward, I grant
you a boon, one of your choosing. Use it
wisely for yourself, a loved one, or a
greater purpose. From this moment, my
grace surrounds you. Walk fearlessly,
for I am always with
you. So, I'm just going to pause here
for a moment. So, what happens when you
complete the main ritual? um like
complete as in complete one cycle of it
whether it's 21 days or or 40 days uh
you will then have this not only just
the vision um as I perceived it but also
this this boon what we so called so
you'll collect this so-called coin it
looks like a coin but it's actually a
boon like a seal and then uh you
can use that in the future towards
greater good for uh
somebody that you would want to benefit
for shanti karma or for good for
somebody's good now people are asking um
can we do can you do it with a real dead
body um I hope not you don't have to uh
this is like I said dya daknachar of
highest quality where you are doing it
all manik when this is happening you
don't have to chant any mantras except
for the mantra in the chanting ing
itself which you can do in your mind and
we are displaying that mantra on the
screen. For all the other mantras you
just have to tap and that's good to do
uh with immersion and people are asking
is it safe to do without a guru?
Uh maybe I should put myself on a loop
and tell you yes yes yes
yes it's it's safe. If it wasn't I
wouldn't have put it out there. I have
not put any sh karma in this uh which I
spoke to about some mohon vashikar and
nuchhat and vidan marun and and stamban
and so on and all those einsteins uh who
are claiming here that this will bring
disastrous consequences and so on they
have absolutely no idea uh what they are
talking about um I speak from experience
I don't just speak from books or from
halfbaked podcasts or preconceived
notions
Uh I speak from experience. I deeply
care about you and I deeply care about
our natan dharma and it is my job to put
the truth out there. Think about it. We
have spent several crores of rupees to
build this app and internally we did not
have that kind of resources. a small
group of uh five people uh in total I
think four people uh five uh one of they
all wish to remain anonymous uh at least
our our biggest uh supporter he wishes
to remain anonymous very very kind
person and um the other one equally kind
very sweet they all stepped in to make
this a reality and our internal
resources um are some of our people took
you know pay cuts to uh to make sure
that we can u support this app, we can
build it. So, um we have not built it to
make money and we're not expecting it to
make money. As I said to you, everything
is free uh in this app. You can do all
the rituals and it's perfectly okay. So,
um so you are totally safe. In fact, if
you are so afraid of divine mother, you
shouldn't be praying at all. Uh you
should uh do what gives you joy. If
you're so afraid of of of mother goddess
then I don't really think you've
understood the very essence of sanatan
dharma. I think
uh you have bought into the lies and the
misguidance of those whose agenda
is not dharma. It is something else.
they are maybe out there constantly um
talking about this and they may appear
very brilliant but it's up to them and
it's entirely your call you can um you
can believe or you may not believe um
either way I'm okay and as I said my job
is to share with you the world um as I
see it if for example you're doing 11
days and in between you miss a day look
it's Not a problem. You just come back
the next day. Um I believe that's how
it's configured. Uh unless of course it
resets to day one in which case well not
a problem again. You just have to spend
a bit more time. And this is also your
portal into Shividya for those of you
who are interested in Shvidya. I will
speak about that um briefly once we
complete this cycle here. Now I wanted
to understand
um would you like to have a sneak peek
at Matara's world? Um because if you do
then I will show you some of that. And
somebody asked
uh can you um
um can you do it on sadna tablet? Yes,
absolutely. It's sheer joy to do it on
Sadna tablet because you get like a
bigger screen and a bigger processor um
and so on. So, okay. So, I'll give you a
sneak preview of Matara's
um sadha which is Shamshanatara Sadha.
Matara is of bluish who she's also
called Neil Saraswati and she's one of
the main goddesses in Buddhism as well.
Like I said, Mahaji nugama came from
her. So this is a little preview one
what happens when we go there you draw
this triangle dik bandan it's called
it's a very very important aspect of uh
sah some people are asking those
repeated questions um so looks like you
were either not here when I started this
stream or you joined later or something
or you did not listen so please just go
back and watch the stream all over again
when it starts I'm just going
go a bit further and further further
further and once he's activated the
dikan which is um activating the 10 of
these each world our team has
painstakingly built each world you know
it's each world is very authentic
um different to how
So then you start your sadhma after you
spread the mat sit on boom and you place
the
skull and like I said this ritual is um
I will just uh so then as you do these
wild animals come but they cannot enter
the triangle so they will stay there.
I'll take you right to the end.
So,
So you'll get now a glimpse of
uh
[Music]
matara. So that's enough. I'll stop
there.
Okay. So, I'll um stop this share here.
So, now you have uh pretty much seen
this um whole thing and just bear in
mind this is the the beginning um of of
the app. This is just the first version.
uh like we have improved the core sadena
app so much. Uh we will improve this app
as well as we go along which would
include um like study materials and
sadhai and and also maybe more tutorials
and like you some of you are asking for
the actual mantras and and and not and
and so on.
So
um now I think it's interesting uh
somebody are saying that how many does
this entire sad require and um and will
33 or 51 days be enough? Um so somebody
said how much did it cost to create this
app? Uh it's several crores of rupees in
the vicinity of around um 7C cr
including uh some of our internal
resources. Um I have nothing to hide. I
am um I'm here to to share everything
with you. I always say ask a question at
your own peril because you will get the
truth and uh truth may not always be
rosy. Now to complete one cycle now I
have to talk to you about Shri Vidya for
a moment. So to complete one cycle of
all 10 worlds will take you roughly 423
days because each world has one day 11
days of preparation uh like preparatory
rituals and then 21 or 40 days of main
ritual. So if you club all that it comes
to 423 days to complete the entire dus
mahavidya cycle which let me tell you
it's just
extraordinarily cheap. It's so easy
because usually uh it can take lifetimes
before anybody gets a even a glimpse or
get exposed to these uh this beautiful
knowledge or is able to do um all these
things.
Now, now once you've done the whole 10
mahavidyas, you will then be required to
do and now this is for those who are
interested in shvidan. I'm telling you
why you will be required to do 10 times
mahatur sundur's cycle again which will
take you roughly 360 days.
Now 423 + 360 is 783 days. So you are
roughly 2 years away 2 years and maybe
two few months maybe two months away
from really doing the fullon shriya
sadhana. So in this one we have
elaborate worship of shri yantra. So
it's it's there. So you are doing shvya
sadna but the actual shri vidya sadha is
about matriur sundri's main sadha which
could be done with punchdashi or shishi
or mahashodishi or even form of
balatriundi and 15 nityas um from
kamehri to mahanita or 16th is mahanita
mother divine herself so kamehalani and
so on so those that whole cycle will
again take time
Could I have hastened the process? I
have done I've expedited it as much as
possible. You see I told you in the very
beginning I do not offer shortcuts. If
there are other people who are offering
you better things faster, please feel
free to go there do that. I do I don't
know
uh what that's like. I only offer you
the real thing and the highest good and
the genuine worship of mother goddess
because I don't dabble with um the lower
forms of energy or anything like that.
Although I have done some of those
sadhas and maybe if in the end it's um
it's it's
um in the end it's required then maybe
it's required. So
um I just would like to thank our team
um BSF's CEO Priyanka um our supporters
uh all those who have supported us over
3 years period every single thing you
did mattered because otherwise we
wouldn't be able to bring you all these
amazing things and our philanthropists
our donors uh like I said five of those
people um who made it possible for us to
roll about something as extraordinary as
this. In a way, this is my lifetime's
work. Um, after this, the pretty much
the only other major um app that I will
work on will be the Shvida app. Uh, but
that's at least
uh a while away. Um, I don't know how
long uh that will take at this stage,
but hopefully if you are doing the whole
10 cycles, by the time you're done with
that, we should be ready uh with that
app. But it's a significant amount of
work and we have not yet raised the full
funding requirements for that. But we've
we've already have commitments. So um we
will start um ASAP. I just have to take
time out for more of that. And um a big
thanks to Vikram Ombut who's our uh
chief operating officer but more
importantly the product lead um on this
who really
really worked day and night um on this.
So um thank you and the entire VSF team
our trustees as well as the development
team uh most of them are based in in
Ukraine. They've
absolutely been mind-blowing uh for us
guys. Thank you so much Alexander. Um
the CEO is also Alexander and the PM is
his name is Alexander. So um thank you
so much. Uh you made it possible for us.
It's been sheer joy to work with you.
I'm saying this because I believe
they've uh joined us uh here as well. So
to answer your question briefly,
initiation is not required. Anybody from
any age can do it. I speak from
experience. I started tantrum so early
on in my life then why can't you? And um
this is the highest form. There is no
punch marker um in it as such. I mean
what you have is just the those
ingredients that you see like shove uh
and so on but you're not consuming
anything. And um I really hope and I
believe that you benefit from it greatly
and that the grace of divine mother
continue to cascade down your
consciousness and your life and you
continue to see the beauty of life um
that there
is. Uh now um somebody's asking should
we stop consumption of alcohol and
smoking? Absolutely no need to stop
anything. uh I mean of course it's good
to not drink uh for your health and not
smoke for your health but not from a
sadna perspective you can start any day
and um you can there is no specific
mhurut you can uh start um any time um
if you somebody's asking if you're a
disciple of another guru can you still
do these sadnas I don't see why not uh
please um absolutely you can and You can
um do this uh do the whole the smidya
with this. Once again this question uh
somebody's asking can girls take break
in sadena during menstruation days. I
mean you can take a break if you want
but um try to stick to the routine
because that's how you train the mind uh
and and consciousness that you
constantly keep doing the same thing
over and over and over and over again
day in day out day in day out day in day
out uh each day every day same time and
your mind starts to shift it starts to
become um very beautiful somebody's
asking can we start with matriund no you
cannot you have to start with makali As
explained right in the beginning um
mahayaka remember that uh you have to
start in this uh
[Music]
and so quite a few people are saying
that they're not able to download this
app and it says device is not compatible
for this app. So I I don't know um what
the solution is but you could maybe go
to tantrasna.app app, our website and I
believe there should be a contact button
there. So you can drop a note to the
support team and hopefully they can then
um tell you um what you can do. they can
guide you uh what you can do
and so I think um thank you to all those
who are saying very positive things um
you know more than um I think around 50
or something full-time people work in
vicad foundation they work very hard to
make this possible for you to experience
uh the beauties and gems of sanatan
dharma and practically
no cost to you. Almost everything is
free um as I understand. So um thank
you. I hope you you like this app. You
go and and use this and uh do something
beautiful with your life. I've taken too
much of your time. On that note, I will
u take your leave. Thank you very much
again. We'll just do a closing chant and
um I deeply appreciate you coming online
and joining me here and I hope um and
you can do this uh dasma vidya sadha
with the other vic sadha you may or may
not be doing your nity karma your other
purushas they can continue as is this
time commitment is not much at all
that's required from you if you want I
mean if you want if you want to stay
healthy you have to work out in the gym
you have to eat right similarly If you
want to experience the world of sadna,
you'll have to take time out for it. I
cannot do anything like that. So, thank
you very much again. We'll do the
closing chant and uh
I I'm very honored and grateful that you
joined
[Music]
me.
for hom.
[Music]
Thank you.